I'd hate to miss that. Ahem.
(Leonard:)Hey, where have you been?
(Sheldon:)Oh, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)If I was prone to sarcasm...
(Sheldon:)...I'd say I was pulling off a major heist
at the Museum of Laundry Baskets.
(Leonard:)One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
(Leonard:)I meant, golly, Sheldon,
you've been gone a long time.
Oh, well, I was waylaid
by Penny, Bernadette and Amy.
(Sheldon:)They made me reveal confidential
information about Howard's father.
- What information?
- I can't tell you that.
I'm bound by closet organizer-organizee
confidentiality.
(Raj:)Come on, we won't tell anyone.
(Sheldon:)Sorry, badgering me won't work.
What you should have said is:
"It's pointless to keep this a secret.
Penny will tell."
- Fine, then that.
- All right, I'll tell you.
(Sheldon:)My goodness,
everyone's on their game today.